<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Caffeine</title>
    <description>Caffeine cuts all the fat out of iOS content loading</description>
    <link>http://caffei.net</link>
    <atom:link href="http://caffei.net/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
      <item>
        <title>How Does Caffeine work?</title>
        <description>
          
          How does Caffeine work? Caffeine is a new internet protocol for app network traffic. We&#39;ve taken HTTP, TLS, and TCP, and re-engineered them into a tightly integrated and faster networking stack. We send the same data you do today, just with less overhead. So if you&#39;re already doing compression and...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 01 Oct 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://caffei.net/2016-10-01-how-does-Caffeine-work/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://caffei.net/2016-10-01-how-does-Caffeine-work/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Caffeine&#39;s Effect on a CDN-Hosted Image</title>
        <description>
          
          The Effect of Caffeine on a CDN’s image We show that delivering an image from Washington D.C. to Austin, TX using Caffeine (1523.8 miles) is far faster than delivering an image from Dallas to Austin using HTTPS (195.1 miles) on a 3G connection. This experiment measures the use of Fastly...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 19 Jun 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://caffei.net/2016-06-19-The-Effect-Of-Caffeine-On-A-CDN/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://caffei.net/2016-06-19-The-Effect-Of-Caffeine-On-A-CDN/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>A Performance Breakthrough on Small File Transfers</title>
        <description>
          
          A performance breakthrough on small file transfers (Codename: LOWTIDE) While testing Nitrogen, the protocol within Caffeine, using small files (&amp;lt;2mb) we discovered peculiar behavior that soon launched an investigation and a subsequent performance breakthrough. Internally, we had conflict. One team thought that Caffeine was going as fast as it could,...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 04 Apr 2016 00:00:00 -0700</pubDate>
        <link>http://caffei.net/2016-04-04-LOWTIDE-Investigation/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://caffei.net/2016-04-04-LOWTIDE-Investigation/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
